VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX | veronika.har@hotmail.com

Profile Summary

A passionate web developer with vast cross-cultural experience (lived and worked in Belarus, China and EU) and a proven record of problem-solving and optimization skills. I can create websites and applications that are fast, efficient, have user-friendly intuitive layouts and responsive designs that look great on any screen size.

Education

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;
- To see my skills in action, visit https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/

MA in Linguistics

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

BA in Linguistics

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

Employment History

Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Supply Chain Specialist | 02/2015 - 07/2016

- ✓ Provided customer service and account management for Qatar Airlines EU freight handling;
- ✓ Analyzed the company's internal S&OP software (AS-TRANS) and cooperated with an outsourced development team on its improvement;

Lear Corporation - Shanghai, China

Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 - 06/2014

- ✓ Lead Logistics Network Optimization for China Seating: identified potential of 20-25% (\$300k annually) savings;
- ✓ Supported LEAR Malaysia Supply Chain recovery;

Generation_P – *Minsk*, *Belarus*

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Node.js

React.js

Redux

React Native

iQuery

APIs

Photoshop

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

TDD

Toolkit

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest/Enzyme

CodePen

GitHub

Chrome Developer Tools

Soft Skills

Supportive

Empathetic

Approachable

Open-minded

Mission driven

Proactive

Adaptable

Collaborative

Open to feedback